blufamilysaver.com 2015-08-22

# bluFamilySaver

## Privacy Policy Statement

This web site is owned and operated by BluFamilySaver.com. We take user privacy seriously and makes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. Please read this policy carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below. This policy applies solely to the web site and our forum all owned by [www.BluFamilySaver.com](http://www.blufamilysaver.com/). 

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at:  

All of the freebies listed on this site are available to the best of our knowledge. 

We find the free offers on other sites and link to them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. 

**_Collection of Personally Identifiable Information_**

Once you apply for an actual free offer on another site other than BluFamilySaver.com, we hold no responsibility for their privacy practices whatsoever. This site is set up purely for fun and we have no control over what other site owners do or do not. 

**_Consumer Information_**

# During the process of delivering an ad to you, BluFamilySaver.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, BluFamilySaver.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by BluFamilySaver.com is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific program, feature, promotion, or ad. If this does occur, BluFamilySaver.com may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition,BluFamilySaver.com may combine this information with other users' information and review. 

# In some cases, software publishers and vendors may ask you to voluntarily provide personal information in order to download their software. BluFamilySaver.com does not collect, use, or have access to this information. This information is collected by the third party publisher or vendor. Users should be advised that they are giving information to a third party. 

**_Opt-out_**

We give you the option to remove your PII from our list of active users or our mailing list at any time. All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be done by clicking the SafeUnsubscribe link at the bottom of your emails at any time. If you wish to Unsubscribe from our forum, please just write to us and we will remove your name and details straight away. 

**_Privacy Policy_**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. BluFamilySaver.com will post those changes on this page. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 1st, 2012
